(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)Every time my dad stayed out
all night,
(Sheldon:)my mom would put hamster poop
in his chewing tobacco.
(Amy:)Well, that's not how
we're going to do it.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)I'm mad at you.
(Sheldon:)Not only did you ruin Raiders for me,
(Sheldon:)you may have ruined
the whole franchise.
(Sheldon:)Except for the fourth one,
(Sheldon:)which was bad
before you got your mitts on it.
(Amy:)I shouldn't have said it.
I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Amy:)-Do you feel better?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)But not as good as I'm going
to when I tell you
(Sheldon:)that your precious Garfield has
no reason to hate Mondays.
(Sheldon:)He's a cat.
He doesn't have a job.
(Leonard:)Hey, I was just--
What is happening?
(Penny:)Oh, just a little treat.
(Penny:)I know you've been feeling really bad
about your mom lately.
(Leonard:)Oh, oh, I have. So bad.